okay I was working out with the uh the
strongman Club on Saturday and they
taught me a new exercise I've never seen
before they don't have Stones um to
practice with so this is what they do
they pile these plates on top of a a 5
lb plate that way you can you can get a
grip underneath but I'm going to start
off and row it to my chest try and get
the plates underneath my chin and then
I'm going to try and lift it up and I'm
trying to pretend like I've got a stone
and I'm trying to lift it up onto a box
you know how they do in the strong man
so anyway here's how it
goes
so you got to keep it tight up I against
your chest or else the plat slide down
anyway cool new exercise thought you
guys would like it